http://www.nedistrict.org/privacy-policy

Contests
2020 Fall - Virtual Convention!
Youth in Harmony
Youth Harmony Workshop Northeast (YHWNE)
NED Seniors Chorus
Resources
Online Virtual Meetings - Find One & Join!
BB/
About Us/MissionHall of Fame 1 - Members/ChaptersHall of Fame 2 - ChorusesHall of Fame 3 - QuartetsNED History / Archive Access--------------------------------2020 NED Leadership TeamCONTACT US - Leadership/ResourcesNews: NED News - 2020 & priorNews: Nor'easter (NED Bulletin) - 2017 & prior--------------------------------LinksNEDACNEWCANEWENGCurrent Openings
Chapters/
Contests/2020 Fall - Virtual Convention!C&J Virtual Assistance-------------------------March COVID-19 Impact / Updates------------------------SCORES ArchivePHOTO ArchivePROGRAMS Archive-----------------------Future Contest Dates - through 20252019 Fall District Convention InfoSeniors Chorus 2020+
Programs/Bachelor of Barbershop HarmonyChapter Achievement ProgramChorus Director DevelopmentStanding Ovation ProgramYouth in HarmonyYouth Harmony Workshop Northeast (YHWNE)NED Seniors Chorus
Resources/Online Virtual Meetings - Find One & Join!-----------------------------------------Chapter Programs/IdeasChapter LeadersContest HostingOfficial DocumentsPHOTO ARCHIVE - ContestsGraphical - Logos - NED & programs
Schools/----------------------------Online Leadership Academy 2020----------------------------Harmony Explosion Camp NortheastHarmony College NE 2020
4FUN/Bulletin BoardAlton Bay JamboreeNew England Harmony BrigadeMixed Harmony Brigade of New England
Contact Us/
GEAR/NEDgear/NEDwear & accessories
members/
Northeastern District of BHS
Barbershop Harmony Society
Privacy Policy
Northeastern District of BHS
Home/
Calendar/
BB/
About Us/MissionHall of Fame 1 - Members/ChaptersHall of Fame 2 - ChorusesHall of Fame 3 - QuartetsNED History / Archive Access--------------------------------2020 NED Leadership TeamCONTACT US - Leadership/ResourcesNews: NED News - 2020 & priorNews: Nor'easter (NED Bulletin) - 2017 & prior--------------------------------LinksNEDACNEWCANEWENGCurrent Openings
Chapters/
Contests/2020 Fall - Virtual Convention!C&J Virtual Assistance-------------------------March COVID-19 Impact / Updates------------------------SCORES ArchivePHOTO ArchivePROGRAMS Archive-----------------------Future Contest Dates - through 20252019 Fall District Convention InfoSeniors Chorus 2020+
Programs/Bachelor of Barbershop HarmonyChapter Achievement ProgramChorus Director DevelopmentStanding Ovation ProgramYouth in HarmonyYouth Harmony Workshop Northeast (YHWNE)NED Seniors Chorus
Resources/Online Virtual Meetings - Find One & Join!-----------------------------------------Chapter Programs/IdeasChapter LeadersContest HostingOfficial DocumentsPHOTO ARCHIVE - ContestsGraphical - Logos - NED & programs
Schools/----------------------------Online Leadership Academy 2020----------------------------Harmony Explosion Camp NortheastHarmony College NE 2020
4FUN/Bulletin BoardAlton Bay JamboreeNew England Harmony BrigadeMixed Harmony Brigade of New England
Contact Us/
GEAR/NEDgear/NEDwear & accessories
members/
General Privacy PolicyNortheastern District of SPEBSQSA Inc., its officers and board of directors, recognize the importance of protecting your personal information. We wouldn’t want anyone to use our personal information without our consent either, so we take protecting yours very seriously. We maintain the following privacy policy:We gather the following types of information:Contact Information You Provide to Us: Such information may be submitted to us via the contact form on our website, email, phone call, social media, our mailing list signup form or any other medium. The types of information that we may collect includes your name, phone number, email addresses, website address, mailing address, social media usernames or any other contact information that you provide to us.Aggregated Tracking Information: We aggregate the behavior of visitors to our website and social media channels in order to better provide services to our visitors. We are able to see aggregated demographic information but are not able to see the identifying information of any individuals unless they publicly share our content in some way.Consumption of Emails We Send: When we send email newsletters to those people that have opted in to receive them, we track who opened these emails as well as who clicked on any of the links placed within the newsletter. We do this to measure what information our email newsletter recipients find valuable in hopes of providing the type of content that a recipient would like to see in the future.We use all of this information to do the following:Communicate with our members, guests, or those that may be interested in talking to us.Track the aggregated use of our website in order to make improvements to the content and structure of our site.Track the behavior of those following us on social media to provide content that is more interesting to our audience.Track the consumption of the content in our email newsletter to inform the content that is included in future newsletters.We do not share, sell or trade your contact information without your consent. We may use your contact information to communicate with you or send you content that you’ve requested, but we will not provide your information to anyone else without first obtaining permission directly from you in writing, on the phone or in person. For members of our district, a specific policy of distribution has been established. You can find this here:  CLICK HEREAny credit information you provide us will be used solely for transactions that you’ve approved. We will never sell, share or provide any of your credit information to any third parties except in the case where we make a purchase on your behalf, in which case we’ll get your approval prior to purchase. We will never use your credit information to make any unapproved purchases.We will at times use cookies to provide you with a more seamless experience when using our website. For instance, we may display specific information to a user that has never visited our site before. Once the new user closes the information, we may use a cookie to help ensure they don’t see that message the next time they visit the Wired Impact site. We also use cookies to collect aggregated website data, including Demographics and Interest Reporting through Google Analytics.We maintain security procedures and standards that we believe are safe and secure. We test these procedures regularly and modify them as new technologies become available. We value the trust you put in us, and we strive to ensure you’ll be able to trust us far into the future.From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to do so when we see fit. Please check periodically to make sure you know our current policies. By using our website, you’re agreeing to the policies outlined on this page.If you have any questions regarding the contents of this Privacy Policy, or any questions in general, please contact us through our District Secretary at secretary@NEDistrict.org..https://members.barbershop.org/pages/data-privacy
The Northeastern District (NED) is one of 17 North American districts and an affiliate/associate entity of the Society for the Preservation and Encouragement of Barber Shop Quartet Singing in America, Inc. (SPEBSQSA, Inc.) aka the "Barbershop Harmony Society".
2021 is our 75th Anniversary year!Founded in 1946, the NED is an IRS 501(c)(3) nonprofit affiliate organization and registered in the Commonwealth of Massachusetts.See Contacts page for details.We serve the northeast region of the United States and Eastern/Atlantic Canada with 45 regional chapters and approximately 1,600 members.  Enjoy this Singing With Us!
Everyone In Harmony.Find a chapter near you!  See above or sitemap - "CHAPTERS"
Select the image above, when it appears,for MORE INFORMATION.Together, Making the Music That's Making a Difference.Copyright © 1998-2020 • All rights reserved.Northeastern District of SPEBSQSA Inc.Official District of the Barbershop Harmony Society NED Webmaster - Steve SalaminMarketing Matters!
•
Make It Happen… now!Privacy PolicySITEMAP:CalendarHOMEAbout UsChaptersContestsProgramsResourcesSchools4FUNContact UsSHEDMembersEveryone In Harmony
